Tufts-New England Medical Center Records MS224
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Planning office records, 1932 -- 1985; 1960 -- 1975; MS224.005; 31.2 Linear Feet
  - Planning library, 1957 -- 1985; MS224.005.001
    - Hospital Planning document 1 - Context, 1970; MS224.005.035.00003; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 35)
    - Hospital Planning document 2 - Adult Programs, 1970; MS224.005.035.00004; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 35)
    - Hospital Planning document 3 - Pediatric Programs, 1969; MS224.005.035.00005; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 35)
    - Hospital Planning document 4 - Non-Medical Programs, 1970; MS224.005.035.00006; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 35)
    - Hospital Planning document 5 - Supply and Services, 1969; MS224.005.035.00007; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 35)
    - Hospital Planning document 6 - Planning Directives, 1970; MS224.005.035.00008; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 35)
    - Hospital Planning document 7 - Appendices, 1970; MS224.005.035.00009; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 35)
    - Report on Housing Demand at T-NEMC, 1970; MS224.005.035.00010; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 35)
    - To Facilitate Health, 1971; MS224.005.035.00011 (Box 35)
    - The Quincy School Project Final Report Year One, 1966 -- 1967; MS224.005.035.00012 (Box 35)
    - A Proposal for a New Program in Medical Education at Tufts University Medical, 1968; MS224.005.035.00013; Tufts University Medical School (Box 35)
    - Hill-Burton Application, 1970; MS224.005.035.00014 (Box 35)
    - Adaptive Housing for the Handicapped, 1971; MS224.005.035.00015; Fishman, Paul L. (Box 35)
    - Panel discussion: crises in dental education, 1963 -- 1966; MS224.005.035.00016 (Box 35)
    - A Feasibility Study of Married Student Housing at T-NEMC, 1965-1975, MS224.005.035.00017; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 35)
    - A Brief on the Status of Proposed Facilities for Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1968; MS224.005.035.00018; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 35)
    - Social Facts by Census Tracts, 1962; MS224.005.035.00019 (Box 35)
    - T-NEMC Master Plan Report, 1970; MS224.005.035.00020; The Architects Collaborative Planning Office T-NEMC (Box 35)
    - Dental Survey Report - Originals, 1967; MS224.005.035.00021 (Box 35)
    - Development of T-NEMC: A Preliminary Study, 1965-1985, 1964; MS224.005.035.00022 (Box 35)
    - Initial Overview Report, 1967; MS224.005.035.00023 (Box 35)
    - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine Clinic Operation Survey Report, 1970; MS224.005.035.00024; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 35)
    - Preliminary Analysis of Educational Facilities, MS224.005.035.00025 (Box 35)
    - Application for a grant for federal funds for construction of teaching facilities, 1970; MS224.005.035.00026; Tufts University Medical School (Box 35)
    - Tufts Dental Health Sciences Building Program, 1970; MS224.005.035.00027; Ehrlich, Edward C.; Eacker, James H. (Box 35)
    - NEMC Hospitals In-Patient Facilities Experimental/Demonstration Project Research Grant Application, 1967; MS224.005.036.00001 (Box 36)
    - Cost-Benefit Analysis MEB, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.036.00002; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 36)
    - A Report on Married Student Housing, #12805, 1969; MS224.005.036.00003; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 36)
    - Planning committee minutes, 1965 -- 1966; MS224.005.036.00004 (Box 36)
    - T-NEMC Master Plan Review (Desk Copy), 1970; MS224.005.036.00005; The Architects Collaborative Inc. (Box 36)
    - Equalized Land Rate Report, 1965; MS224.005.036.00006 (Box 36)
    - Memo - Taxes for Facilities, 1963 -- 1975; MS224.005.036.00007; Boston Redevelopment Authority; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 36)
    - T-NEMC Andover Planning Conference, 1968; MS224.005.036.00008 (Box 36)
    - Final Functional Program NEMC Hospitals, 1968; MS224.005.036.00009 (Box 36)
    - Health Facilities Laboratory Inc., 1971; MS224.005.036.00010 (Box 36)
    - T-NEMC Development Funds - Budgets and Balance Sheets, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.036.00011 (Box 36)
    - Quincy School Community Council reports and general progress, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.036.00012 (Box 36)
    - Quincy School Community Council minutes, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.005.036.00013 (Box 36)
    - Quincy School Health Project minutes, 1968; MS224.005.036.00014 (Box 36)
    - Quincy School Community Council minutes, 1968 -- 1969; MS224.005.036.00015 (Box 36)
    - A Matter of Self-Respect, MS224.005.036.00016; Maloney, William F. (Box 36)
    - Design Requirements for the Quincy School Complex (Draft), 1970; MS224.005.036.00017 (Box 36)
    - Remarks of Hermann H. Field at the citizens seminar on the fiscal, economic and political problems of boston and the metropolitan community, 1961; MS224.005.036.00018 (Box 36)
    - Application of Comprehensive Planning to the Urban Teaching Medical Center, 1964; MS224.005.036.00019; Field, Hermann H. (Box 36)
    - Health Information Sciences Committee report, 1968; MS224.005.036.00020 (Box 36)
    - Research, Management, and New Product Development Volume 1, 1965; MS224.005.036.00021 (Box 36)
    - Reflections on Dental Education and Community Dental Health Services, 1966-1970, MS224.005.036.00022 (Box 36)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1966 -- 1970; MS224.005.036.00023 (Box 36)
    - Architectural plans, 1975; MS224.005.036.00024 (Box 36)
    - NECH inpatient admission survey report, 1969; MS224.005.037.00001; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 37)
    - Publications and maps, 1965 -- 1970; MS224.005.037.00002 (Box 37)
    - Final Elevatoring Report, 1969; MS224.005.037.00003 (Box 37)
    - Proceedings of A Special Conference on Health Facilities Research, 1970; MS224.005.037.00004 (Box 37)
    - Proposal for the Construction of Parking Facilities at the T-NEMC, 1969; MS224.005.037.00005; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 37)
    - Quincy School Planning Project proposal for a planning grant, 1966 -- 1968; MS224.005.037.00006 (Box 37)
    - Health Facilities Laboratory Study Group meetings, 1971; MS224.005.037.00007 (Box 37)
    - Roster of Participants and Observers Andover Planning Conference, 1969; MS224.005.037.00008 (Box 37)
    - T-NEMC Andover Planning Conference - Plan and Program Schedule, 1969; MS224.005.037.00009 (Box 37)
    - Schematic Elevator Review, 1969; MS224.005.037.00010; Charles W. Lerch & Associates Elevator Consulting Engineers (Box 37)
    - Study of Existing Facilities and New Possibilities for the Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1962; MS224.005.037.00011; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 37)
    - T-NEMC memorandum - parking, 1969; MS224.005.037.00012 (Box 37)
    - Proposal for the Construction of Parking Facilities at the T-NEMC, 1969; MS224.005.037.00013 (Box 37)
    - Health Facilities Laboratory, MS224.005.037.00014 (Box 37)
    - Medical Center Planning and Design Within the Total Urban Setting, 1969; MS224.005.037.00015 (Box 37)
    - The Quincy School Project, 1969; MS224.005.037.00016; Quincy School Community Council; Quincy School Project Staff; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 37)
    - Workbook for Program Evaluation Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1967; MS224.005.051.00001 (Box 51)
    - Tufts University Dental Clinics - A Manual of Administration, 1964 -- 1965; MS224.005.051.00002 (Box 51)
    - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine Data Processing Feasibility Study, 1965; MS224.005.051.00003 (Box 51)
    - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine application for a grant of federal funds for construction of teaching facilities, 1965; MS224.005.051.00004 (Box 51)
    - Public Health Service construction application, 1968; MS224.005.051.00005 (Box 51)
  - General files, 1932 -- 1976; MS224.005.002
    - Urban renewal: institutions and committees, MS224.005.037.00017 (Box 37)
    - Alternate strategies for development of basic scientific facilities and memo, 1969; MS224.005.037.00018 (Box 37)
    - Blue sky reports, 1968; MS224.005.037.00019 (Box 37)
    - Cost-benefit analysis, MS224.005.037.00020 (Box 37)
    - Educational unit, 1968; MS224.005.037.00021 (Box 37)
    - Library, 1968; MS224.005.037.00022 (Box 37)
    - Mental health office of the mayor, 1968; MS224.005.037.00023 (Box 37)
    - Space description form, MS224.005.037.00024 (Box 37)
    - Research and department offices, MS224.005.037.00025 (Box 37)
    - Research and department offices - Microbiology, 1969; MS224.005.037.00026 (Box 37)
    - Research and department offices - Biochemistry, MS224.005.037.00027 (Box 37)
    - Research and department offices - Anatomy (Micro and Gross), MS224.005.037.00028 (Box 37)
    - Research and department officies - Pathology, 1969; MS224.005.037.00029 (Box 37)
    - Research and department offices - Physiology, MS224.005.037.00030 (Box 37)
    - MEB project outline, 1969; MS224.005.037.00031 (Box 37)
    - Phase II: faculty committees (general), 1966 -- 1969; MS224.005.037.00032 (Box 37)
    - Phase II: program notes (general), 1969; MS224.005.037.00033 (Box 37)
    - General notes, 1968 -- 1969; MS224.005.037.00034 (Box 37)
    - Administrative unit, MS224.005.037.00035 (Box 37)
    - Boy scouts, 1968; MS224.005.037.00036 (Box 37)
    - City health, MS224.005.037.00037 (Box 37)
    - Podiatry unit, 1968; MS224.005.037.00038 (Box 37)
    - Welfare, MS224.005.037.00039 (Box 37)
    - YWCA, 1968; MS224.005.037.00040 (Box 37)
    - Urban renewal: institutions and committees, 1956 -- 1963; MS224.005.037.00041 (Box 37)
    - Allocation of MEB copies, MS224.005.037.00042 (Box 37)
    - Administration, MS224.005.037.00043 (Box 37)
    - Previous planning files on TUSM - #11435, 1962; MS224.005.037.00044 (Box 37)
    - Previous planning files on TUSM - #11436, 1962; MS224.005.037.00045 (Box 37)
    - Previous planning files on TUSM - #11438, 1962; MS224.005.037.00046 (Box 37)
    - Previous planning files on TUSM - #11439, 1962; MS224.005.037.00047 (Box 37)
    - Previous planning files on TUSM - #11441, 1962; MS224.005.037.00048 (Box 37)
    - Previous planning files on TUSM - #11442, 1962; MS224.005.037.00049 (Box 37)
    - Previous planning files on TUSM - #11443, 1962; MS224.005.037.00050 (Box 37)
    - Previous planning files on TUSM - #11444, 1962; MS224.005.037.00051 (Box 37)
    - Driving time (maps), 1966 -- 1969; MS224.005.037.00052 (Box 37)
    - Dental school memo for hallowell, 1968; MS224.005.037.00053 (Box 37)
    - Joint application - organization and notes, 1969; MS224.005.037.00054 (Box 37)
    - Curriculum diagrams, MS224.005.037.00055 (Box 37)
    - Phase I: material, 1969; MS224.005.037.00056 (Box 37)
    - Dental program for disadvantaged, 1968; MS224.005.037.00057 (Box 37)
    - Objectives, 1967 -- 1969; MS224.005.037.00058 (Box 37)
    - Nursing report - Miss Katz, 1965; MS224.005.037.00059 (Box 37)
    - Nursing: House Survey, 1966; MS224.005.037.00060 (Box 37)
    - Housing strategy, 1967; MS224.005.037.00061 (Box 37)
    - Hill-Burton application guide, MS224.005.037.00062 (Box 37)
    - Grant award notices, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.005.037.00063 (Box 37)
    - Fund raising committee, 1967; MS224.005.037.00064 (Box 37)
    - Floating Hospital, 1972; MS224.005.037.00065 (Box 37)
    - Tufts - Bylaws, 1962; MS224.005.037.00066 (Box 37)
    - Trustees, 1965 -- 1969; MS224.005.037.00067 (Box 37)
    - T-NEMC suggested program and land distribution, MS224.005.037.00068 (Box 37)
    - T-NEMC photos, MS224.005.037.00069 (Box 37)
    - Previous planning files on TUSM - #11440, 1962; MS224.005.037.00070 (Box 37)
    - Previous planning files on TUSM - #11437, 1962; MS224.005.037.00071 (Box 37)
    - Comprehensive health care for children - #12009, 1963; MS224.005.037.00072; Eliot, Martha M. (Box 37)
    - Parking, MS224.005.037.00073 (Box 37)
    - Coonamassett Conference, 1970; MS224.005.037.00074 (Box 37)
    - Planning office reconnaissance study, 1969; MS224.005.037.00075 (Box 37)
    - T-NEMC personnel and policies, 1969 -- 1972; MS224.005.037.00076 (Box 37)
    - T-NEMC job study, 1968; MS224.005.038.00001 (Box 38)
    - Personnel, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.005.038.00002 (Box 38)
    - Director of Facilities and Capital Planning - responsibilities, duties and procedures, 1969 -- 1973; MS224.005.038.00003 (Box 38)
    - Task force - extended care, 1967 -- 1968; MS224.005.038.00004 (Box 38)
    - Ambulatory care - task force minutes, MS224.005.038.00005 (Box 38)
    - T-NEMC incorporation agreement, T-NEMC bylaws, 1969; MS224.005.038.00006 (Box 38)
    - T-NEMC affiliation agreement, 1970; MS224.005.038.00007 (Box 38)
    - TAC, 1968; MS224.005.038.00008 (Box 38)
    - Tax exempt papers, 1932 -- 1969; MS224.005.038.00009 (Box 38)
    - Speech for Hermann H. Field commercial building conference, 1966; MS224.005.038.00010 (Box 38)
    - Quarles notes on Andover conference, 1967; MS224.005.038.00011 (Box 38)
    - Planning office review (public relations), 1967; MS224.005.038.00012 (Box 38)
    - Report on planning - Field, 1961 -- 1967; MS224.005.038.00013 (Box 38)
    - Planning committee actions, 1967 -- 1968; MS224.005.038.00014 (Box 38)
    - Fringe benefits - NEMC and Tufts, 1970; MS224.005.038.00015 (Box 38)
    - Ed Ehrlich correspondence, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.005.038.00016 (Box 38)
    - Metropolitan building, 1972; MS224.005.038.00017 (Box 38)
    - Metropolitan building - conduit under Washington street, 1972; MS224.005.038.00018 (Box 38)
    - NEMCH financial report, 1973; MS224.005.038.00019 (Box 38)
    - NEMCH certificate of need acts, 1972; MS224.005.038.00020 (Box 38)
    - NEMCH coffee shop, 1970; MS224.005.038.00021 (Box 38)
    - EEO files - Barr and Barr estimates and analysis - Dental, 1970; MS224.005.038.00022 (Box 38)
    - Eacker, James, 1971; MS224.005.038.00023 (Box 38)
    - Equal employment opportunity, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.005.038.00024 (Box 38)
    - EEO - Chinese community, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.005.038.00025 (Box 38)
    - EEO - pre-award conferences, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.038.00026 (Box 38)
    - EEO - Boston plan, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.038.00027 (Box 38)
    - EEO - Contractors Association of Boston, 1971; MS224.005.038.00028 (Box 38)
    - EEO - Chinese American Civic Association Multi-service Center, 1971; MS224.005.038.00029 (Box 38)
    - EEO - NEMCH renovations, 1971; MS224.005.038.00030 (Box 38)
    - EEO - parking garage, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.038.00031 (Box 38)
    - EEO - phase III, 1971; MS224.005.038.00032 (Box 38)
    - Equal employment opportunity notes, 1967 -- 1971; MS224.005.038.00033 (Box 38)
    - EEO - Intercollegiate Construction Council, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.038.00034 (Box 38)
    - Master plan surveys, 1962; MS224.005.038.00035 (Box 38)
    - Office architecture - 6206, 1962; MS224.005.038.00036 (Box 38)
    - Office architecture - 6207, 1963; MS224.005.038.00037 (Box 38)
    - Office architecture - 6208, MS224.005.038.00038 (Box 38)
    - Office architecture - 6209, 1963; MS224.005.038.00039 (Box 38)
    - Office architecture - 6301, 1963 -- 1964; MS224.005.038.00040 (Box 38)
    - Office architecture - 6302, 1963; MS224.005.038.00041 (Box 38)
    - Office architecture - 6401, 1964; MS224.005.038.00042 (Box 38)
    - Office architecture - 6402, 1964; MS224.005.038.00043 (Box 38)
    - Spouge space, 1967; MS224.005.038.00044 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967; MS224.005.038.00045 (Box 38)
    - Dean's office 4th floor - 6607, 1966 -- 1967; MS224.005.038.00046 (Box 38)
    - Purchasing, 1967; MS224.005.038.00047 (Box 38)
    - Personnel, 1967; MS224.005.038.00048 (Box 38)
    - Psychiatry - 6605, 1966; MS224.005.038.00049 (Box 38)
    - Preclinical Labs - 6602, 1966; MS224.005.038.00050 (Box 38)
    - Nursing Remodelling - 6601, 1966 -- 1967; MS224.005.038.00051 (Box 38)
    - Oral pediatrics - 6603, 1966; MS224.005.038.00052 (Box 38)
    - Job training programs, 1971; MS224.005.038.00053 (Box 38)
    - Materials Handling Task Force meetings and information, 1967 -- 1968; MS224.005.048.00001 (Box 48)
    - Materials Handling Task Force cyber rail, 1967; MS224.005.048.00002 (Box 48)
    - Materials Handling Task Force meeting minutes, 1968; MS224.005.048.00003 (Box 48)
    - Materials Handling Task Force meeting minutes, 1968; MS224.005.048.00004 (Box 48)
    - Planning Department minutes, 1968; MS224.005.048.00005 (Box 48)
    - Materials Handling Task Force memos, meetings, reports, 1968; MS224.005.048.00006 (Box 48)
    - Charles T. Main correspondence and reports, 1968; MS224.005.048.00007 (Box 48)
    - Charles T. Main correspondence and reports, 1965 -- 1967; MS224.005.048.00008 (Box 48)
    - Charles T. Main project, coding, 1967; MS224.005.048.00009 (Box 48)
    - Charles T. Main project, coding, 1966 -- 1967; MS224.005.048.00010 (Box 48)
    - Industrial Engineering Pilot Studies at NEMCH, 1966; MS224.005.048.00011; Charles T. Main, Inc. (Box 48)
    - NEMCH Industrial Engineering Study of Hospital Operations Progress Bulletin No. 3, 1966; MS224.005.048.00012; Charles T. Main, Inc. (Box 48)
    - NEMCH Progress Report Recommendations of Materials Handling Systems, Facilities, and Equipment for a Projected Future Hospital, 1965; MS224.005.048.00013; Charles T. Main, Inc. (Box 48)
    - Report on Proposed Total Study Plan NEMCH, 1966; MS224.005.048.00014; Charles T. Main, Inc. (Box 48)
    - NEMCH Industrial Engineering Study Part I, 1967; MS224.005.048.00015; Charles T. Main, Inc. (Box 48)
    - NEMCH Industrial Engineering report, 1967; MS224.005.048.00016; Charles T. Main, Inc. (Box 48)
    - NEMCH Industrial Engineering Report Abstract, 1967; MS224.005.048.00017; Charles T. Main, Inc. (Box 48)
    - T-NEMC Report on Economic Comparison of Proposed Materials Handling Systems, 1968; MS224.005.048.00018; Charles T. Main, Inc. (Box 48)
    - Proger building "Telelift" system loose papers, 1968 -- 1971; MS224.005.048.00019 (Box 48)
    - Pneumatic Tube System Questionnaire Telelift Data, 1970; MS224.005.048.00020 (Box 48)
    - Telelift system proposal, 1970; MS224.005.048.00021 (Box 48)
    - Cyber rail data, 1967 -- 1969; MS224.005.048.00022 (Box 48)
    - Price Waterhouse and Company, 1968; MS224.005.048.00023 (Box 48)
    - AMSCO - American Sterilizer Company, 1968 -- 1969; MS224.005.048.00024 (Box 48)
    - Souder, James, 1968; MS224.005.048.00025 (Box 48)
    - Materials handling literature and architectural drawings, 1968 -- 1969; MS224.005.048.00026 (Box 48)
    - Proger 1A furniture and equipment, 1970; MS224.005.048.00027 (Box 48)
    - NEMCH 1A inpatient dental space tabulation, 1971; MS224.005.048.00028 (Box 48)
    - Employee notices of withdrawel, 1965 -- 1972; MS224.005.048.00029 (Box 48)
    - TMCA contract, 1976; MS224.005.048.00030 (Box 48)
  - Master plan files, 1954 -- 1972; MS224.005.003
    - Master plan - development housing Shafik's report, MS224.005.038.00054 (Box 38)
    - Master plan - projections - model, 1962; MS224.005.038.00055 (Box 38)
    - Master plan - student union - student needs, 1962; MS224.005.038.00056 (Box 38)
    - Master plan - projections, MS224.005.039.00001 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing development housing, MS224.005.039.00002 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing, 1961 -- 1962; MS224.005.039.00003 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing - elderly application forms, 1961 -- 1962; MS224.005.039.00004 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing - financing, 1962; MS224.005.039.00005 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - dental school bibliography, 1961; MS224.005.039.00006 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - circulation - analysis, 1961; MS224.005.039.00007 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - dental school - dental manufacturers, MS224.005.039.00008 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - dental school - dentist's office, 1963; MS224.005.039.00009 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - dental school - N.S.F. reports, MS224.005.039.00010 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - design, 1963; MS224.005.039.00011 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - Floating Hospital, 1962; MS224.005.039.00012 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - function - community needs, 1962; MS224.005.039.00013 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - goals - T-NEMC operations, MS224.005.039.00014 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing - college housing loans applications, 1954 -- 1962; MS224.005.039.00015 (Box 39)
    - Master program - capital program, costs, public works, MS224.005.039.00016 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - circulation - parking, 1962 -- 1963; MS224.005.039.00017 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - circulation - pedestrian traffic survey, 1962; MS224.005.039.00018 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - circulation - preliminary study, 1961; MS224.005.039.00019 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - consultants - Kevin Lynch, 1955; MS224.005.039.00020 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - dental center - dental lectures, 1962; MS224.005.039.00021 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - dental center - office survey, 1962; MS224.005.039.00022 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - acquisitions, 1962 -- 1964; MS224.005.039.00023 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - acquisitions - demolitions, 1962; MS224.005.039.00024 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - circulation - traffic volumes, 1956 -- 1958; MS224.005.039.00025 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - building plans - TNEMC, 1963; MS224.005.039.00026 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - acquisitions - property maps, 1960; MS224.005.039.00027 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - acquisitions - 112 credits, 1962; MS224.005.039.00028 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - Bradford Hotel memos, 1965; MS224.005.039.00029 (Box 39)
    - Inventory - existing plans - Sanborn maps, MS224.005.039.00030 (Box 39)
    - Inventory - T-NEMC plans, 1962 -- 1963; MS224.005.039.00031 (Box 39)
    - Inventory - T-NEMC delivery survey, 1963; MS224.005.039.00032 (Box 39)
    - Inventory - PC/NECH plans, MS224.005.039.00033 (Box 39)
    - Iventory - Survey interface, MS224.005.039.00034 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - population, students, 1961; MS224.005.039.00035 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing - married students, maps, drawings, MS224.005.039.00036 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing - Married students, tables, 1965 -- 1966; MS224.005.039.00037 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing MIT, 1963; MS224.005.039.00038 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - plans proposed site plan 1980 prints, 1963; MS224.005.039.00039 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - implementation - staging, MS224.005.039.00040 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - library standards, MS224.005.039.00041 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - MBTA subway, 1965; MS224.005.039.00042 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - metropolitan transit authority, Forest Hills line, 1963; MS224.005.039.00043 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - parking, MS224.005.039.00044 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - PERT-Outline Network, MS224.005.039.00045 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - proposed site plan 1980 sepias, 1963; MS224.005.039.00046 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing - rehab housing, 1961; MS224.005.039.00047 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing - realtors, 1961; MS224.005.039.00048 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing - university, 1961 -- 1962; MS224.005.039.00049 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing - married student interviews, 1965; MS224.005.039.00050 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - BFH physical facilities, questionnaire, 1962; MS224.005.039.00051 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - land, building, space inventory, 1962; MS224.005.039.00052 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - acquisitions - metro property, 1962; MS224.005.039.00053 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing - geriatric nursing homes, 1961; MS224.005.039.00054 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - housing - high rise, 1962; MS224.005.039.00055 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - employee control sheets, 1961; MS224.005.039.00056 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - employee, 1961; MS224.005.039.00057 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - student union - fraternities, 1962; MS224.005.039.00058 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - dental center - general, 1962 -- 1963; MS224.005.039.00059 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - office facilities - private, 1961; MS224.005.039.00060 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - pedestrian circulation - volunteer instructions, MS224.005.039.00061 (Box 39)